(knocks)
(Sheldon:)Come in.
(cats meowing)
(Amy:)Surprise.
(Sheldon:)Mom, what an unexpected pleasure.
(Mrs Cooper:)My, my, that's a powerful smell.
(Sheldon:)I'd like you to meet Oppenheimer,
Frisch, Panofsky,
(Sheldon:)Feynman, Weisskopf...
(Mrs Cooper:)Yeah, I get it.
(Mrs Cooper:)You got a lot of cats
(Mrs Cooper:)and you gave 'em cute Jewish names.
(Sheldon:)What are you doing here?
(Mrs Cooper:)Leonard called.
(Mrs Cooper:)And he said that you were
pining for a young lady.
(Sheldon:)Oh, that's preposterous.
(Sheldon:)I'm not pining over anyone.
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, lambchop, we can
quibble what to call it,
(Mrs Cooper:)but I think we can
both agree it's creepy.
(Sheldon:)I do not agree.
(Sheldon:)Cats make wonderful companions.
(Sheldon:)They don't argue or question
my intellectual authority,
(Sheldon:)and this little guy here,
(Sheldon:)I think you'll find
to be quite zazzy.
(Mrs Cooper:)You should have called sooner.